Okay, now in this lecture, I'm going to do a quick hands on on inference parameters.
So I'm on the Amazon bedrock service.
So if we just go to this chat and text playground and just select a model here,
maybe I'll select Amazon, Nova Pro on demand inference and do I apply.
Okay, now on the left hand side, you can see all the inference parameters.
So you have length, maximum output token size.
So to control length, you can use this maximum output tokens.
So here, you can see it varies between one to five thousand sixty three.
But if you go and select some of the models from entropic,
it has up to sixty four thousand max output token size.
Then here, you can add stop sequence.
So maybe I can just add a character and this is my stop sequence closing curly bracket.
I can just do add and then you can add some more stop sequence.
If you want, then you have the randomness and diversity
where you can determine the temperature, which defines the creativity of the model.
So if I just click here, influence the probability of selecting output with different
likelihoods, choose the higher value if you want to generate more creative response.
So here for this Amazon, Nova Pro model, the temperature values would be zero to one.
But in some models, it can be between zero to five.
So if I want a highly creative response, then I give one.
If I want a very predictable response, I give it as zero.
Then you have the top K and if you just click on this,
limits the percentage of candidates to consider in generation.
The model considers top P percent of the candidates.
P percent of the candidates where P is the value you choose, choose the higher value
to consider more candidates.
And here again, you have the option to choose between 0.1 and 1.
Okay, let me just set the response. So we have a highly predictive answer.
So let me just move to zero and let me just pose a question.
And let me just say who is the best football player in the world?
And now if I just do a run.
So it has given us a very predictable list.
So Lionel Messi, Cristiano Ronaldo and some other names.
So if you just see here, so it has given us number of input tokens, which was our question.
So it was 11 input tokens, then output the output it has generated,
which is 280 tokens, then it also shows us latency.
So you can see her max output tokens are 5, 0, 6, 3, but it stopped at 282 tokens.
So which means it has used its internal mechanism to stop the output response
after a certain number of tokens.
And that would most likely be based on its training data.
Okay, so that's pretty much it from this lecture. I'll see you in the next lecture. Thank you.